Quirini, Helen; Papers apap102
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Work, Union and Politics, 1933-2007; Undated; 2; 9.9 cubic ft.
  - U.S. Department of Labor Literature, 1956; 1967; 1970 (Box 9 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 1)
  - Voting Schedule, UE Local 301, Undated (Box 9 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 2)
  - Wallace, Henry, 1948; Undated (Box 9 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 3)
  - What to do About Communism in Unions by L.R. Boulware, 1952 (Box 9 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 4)
  - Work Chronology for Helen Quirini, Undated (Box 9 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 5)
  - Zahavi, 1992 August 24 (Cassette 23)
- Women and Work, 1942-2009; Undated; 3; 2.9 cubic ft.
  This series deals with the specific issue of women's rights and representation in the workplace and union. It contains significant materials, including correspondence, agendas, resolutions and news clippings, about UE and IUE women's conferences (both national and regional), educational programs and committees. Helen Quirini attended and spoke at many of these events and her handwritten notes are often included among the materials. Subject files discuss such topics as equal pay for equal work, automation, pay rates and the Equal Rights Amendment. There are files with records from speaking events featuring Quirini, Quirini's notes from the shop floor on the treatment of women and her later writings about the discrimination she encountered at General Electric as a female employee. In addition, there is UE, IUE, AFL-CIO and U.S. Department of Labor literature on women workers collected by Quirini.
  Quirini was active in the Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW). She attended its founding conference in Chicago in 1974 and many subsequent national conferences and was involved in its Capital District chapter during the 1980s. The nonpartisan CLUW brought together women from various trade unions to address shared concerns to common problems. It remains the only national organization for women workers in the United States.
  - Abortion Rights and Working Women, 1983; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO and CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1975; 1977; 1979 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 2)
  - AFSCME and AFL-CIO Literature on Women, 1971; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 3)
  - Automation and Women Workers, 1970; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 4)
  - Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1983; 1986-1990; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 5)
  - Buttons and Ribbons, Including Ones About International Women's Year, Working Women, Women in Unions, 1975; Undated (Oversized 7)
  - Channel 17, Equal Rights Amendment, Women's Movement, 1975 (Cassette 24)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Boycott of J.P. Stevens, Textile Products, 1977; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 6)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Capital District, 1976; 1981; 1984; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 7)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Chapter Presidents, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 8)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Constitutions and Constitutional Convention, 1975; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 9)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Delegated Convention Proposal, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 10)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Elections, 1975-1976; 1982-1983; 1991; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 11)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) First Biennial Convention, 1979; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 12)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Founding Conference, 1974; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 13)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) General Correspondence, 1975-1977; 1979; 1982; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 14)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Literature, 1974; 1976; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 15)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Membership and Recruitment, 1976; 1987; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 16)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) New Jersey, 1974-1975; 1979; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 17)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) New York, 1976 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 18)
  - CLUW News, 1975-1979; 1982-1985 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 19)
  - CLUW News, 1986-1991 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 20)
  - CLUW News, 1992-1996; 1999 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 21)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Rank and File Caucus, Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 22)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Resolutions Approved by National Coordinating Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 23)
  - CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women) Third Biennial Convention, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 24)
  - Committee for a Class Struggle CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women), Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 25)
  - "Discrimination GE Style for 29 Years," Submitted by Helen Quirini to Beating Our Wings, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 26)
  - Education Program for Union Women, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 27)
  - Electrical Union News Articles About Women in the Workplace, Especially Pay Rates, 1942-1945; 1947; 1952-1954 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 28)
  - Emily Skidmore, Making Room for Many Worlds, Undated (Cd 8)
  - Equal Employment Opportunities and Sex Discrimination Laws, 1966-1979; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 29)
  - Equal Pay, 1970; 1981; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 30)
  - Equal Rights Amendment and Labor, 1970; 1973; 1975-1981; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 31)
  - Everywoman's Day Program, College of St. Rose, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 32)
  - Facts on Women Workers, Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 33)
  - Female Distribution by Job Rate at General Electric, 1970; 1973; 1975-1980; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 34)
  - Fliers about Women Workers and Sex Discrimination, Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 35)
  - "The Fight for Women Workers' Rights," by UE District Councils Four and Eleven, 1952 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 36)
  - General Correspondence About Women and Work, 1970; 1976; 1983; 1995; 1997 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 37)
  - Histories of UE and IUE in fight for Women's Rights, 1996; 2003; 2009; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 38)
  - It's Our Economy, Isn't It? Conference, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 39)
  - IUE Anti-Discrimination Efforts at General Electric, 1973; 1975-1976; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 40)
  - IUE Constitutional Convention Resolutions on Working Women and International Women's Year, 1967-1969; 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 41)
  - IUE Discrimination Legal Guide, 1976; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 42)
  - IUE District Three Annual Women's Conference, 1970 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 43)
  - IUE District Three First Women's Conference, 1969 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 44)
  - IUE District Three Women's Conference, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 45)
  - IUE District Three Women's Conference, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 46)
  - IUE District Three Women's Conference, 1980 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 47)
  - IUE District Three Women's Conference Resolutions, Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 48)
  - IUE Districts One and Three Salute to Women, Including Helen Quirini Certificate, 1974; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 49)
  - IUE History of Helping Working Women in The IUE News, 1986 (Oversized 1, Folder 9)
  - IUE News "The Woman Worker and the IUE", 1975 (Oversized 3, Folder 2)
  - IUE Northeast Regional Social Action and Women's Conference, 1974 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 50)
  - IUE Northeast Regional Social Action and Women's Conference, 1976 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 51)
  - IUE Statistics on Women Workers and Related Questionnaire Completed by Helen Quirini, 1972; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 52)
  - IUE Women's Conference, 1980 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 53)
  - IUE Women's Council, Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 54)
  - IUE/UE Switch, IUE Propaganda for Women, Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 55)
  - IUE/UE Switch, UE Propaganda for Women, 1954; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 56)
  - "The Life and Times of Rosie the Riveter" Program with Helen Quirini, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 57)
  - Minutes of General Electric and IUE Meeting on discrimination of Women, 1969 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 58)
  - National Commission on Working Women, 1975-1979 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 59)
  - National Commission on the International Women's Year, 1975 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 60)
  - National Commission on Working Women Women at Work Newsletters, 1983-1986; 1988-1992; Undated (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 61)
  - "Never Underestimate the Power of a Woman", 1953 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 62)
  - New York State Department of Labor Report on Women in Jobs, 1957 (Box 1 (3-Women and Work), Folder 63)
  - New York State Women's Unit/Conference and Meeting, 1967; 1970-1971; 1977 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings About or Mentioning Helen Quirini, 1952-1953; 1970-1971; 1995; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 2)
  - Notes from Helen Quirini on Women and Work, Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 3)
  - Organization Matters: Early UE Experiences Fighting the Economic Exploitation of Women Workers by Carol Lambiase, 2002 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 4)
  - Paradoxical Impact, Lisa, 1991 (Cassette 25)
  - Paradoxical Impact of the Cold War on Women's Trade Union, 1991 October (Cassette 26)
  - Pay Rate Data for Helen Quirini, 1953-1970; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 5)
  - Pay Rates at General Electric, 1948; 1972; 1975; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 6)
  - Rosie the Riveter, Panel Discussion, Undated (Cassette 27)
  - Shop Floor Notes by Helen Quirini on Issues Affecting Women and Discrimination, 1954; 1973-1974 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 7)
  - Significant Women, Rutgers College, 1998 May (Video-tape 60)
  - Significant Women, Union College, 1998 April 03-1998 April 04 (Video-tape 61)
  - Speaking Events Featuring Helen Quirini, Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 8)
  - Statements by IUE on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 9)
  - Survey of Women Workers, Possibly at General Electric, Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 10)
  - Trade Union Women's Studies, Cornell University, 1971; 1976; 1984; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 11)
  - UE 1st National Conference on the Problems of Working Women, 1953; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 12)
  - UE 2nd National Conference on the Problems of Working Women, 1954; 2007; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 13)
  - UE 4th National Conference on the Problems of Working Women, 1956 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 14)
  - UE Conference on Women's Rates in GE, 1953; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 15)
  - UE District 11 Women's Conference, 1952 (Oversized 1, Folder 10)
  - UE District Four Conference for Women's Rights, 1952 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 16)
  - UE District Three Women's Conference, 1952 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 17)
  - UE History of Fighting Discrimination in UE News, 1976 (Oversized 1, Folder 11)
  - UE Literature About Women, 1952-1953; 1971; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 18)
  - UE Local 301, Women's Committee Meetings, 1946; 1953; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 19)
  - UE National Fair Practices Committee, 1954; Undated (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 20)
  - UE National Women's Conference, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 21)
  - UE Women's Conference, Helen Quirini Speech, 1954 May 15 (Cassette 28)
  - Union Proposal for Re-Slotting of Women's Jobs at GE Euclid Lamp, 1953 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 22)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Handbook of Facts on Women Workers, 1950; 1952 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 23)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Handbook on Women Workers, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Women and Work), Folder 24)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Literature on Women, 1942; 1944-1945 (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 1)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Literature on Women, 1951-1956 (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 2)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Literature on Women, 1965; 1967-1970 (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 3)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Literature on Women, 1971-1973 (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 4)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Literature on Women, 1976-1980 (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 5)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Literature on Women, Undated (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 6)
  - Virginia Slims American Women's Opinion Poll, 1980 (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 7)
  - Women of Achievement, 2007 April 10 (Dvd 15)
  - Women in the Economy, Human Productivity and the Nature of Work Conference, 1976 (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 8)
  - Women in the IUE, 1967 (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 9)
  - Women in Service, Undated (Video-tape 62)
  - Women Returning to Work Conference, 1981 (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 10)
  - Women's Anticipated Earning Rate Case, 1947; Undated (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 11)
  - Women's Conference, 1950 (Video-tape 63)
  - Women's History Month, Shirley Chisolm, 1988 March (Video-tape 64)
  - Women's Rights, Women Won't Take No for an Answer, Undated (Cd 9)
  - Women's Suffrage, Undated (Video-tape 65)
  - UE Women's Leadership Roundtable, 2003 August 26 (Video-tape 66)
  - Young, Ruth, 1943; 2004; Undated (Box 3 (3-Women and Work), Folder 12)
- Labor Newspapers, 1917-1987; Undated; 4; 3.2 cubic ft. plus 9 microfilm reels
  Arranged chronologically by publication.
  This series contains both labor union and General Electric newspapers collected by Helen Quirini while employed at General Electric and during her retirement. The newspapers include publications of other local unions, regional groups and national organizations. Newspaper clippings about or mentioning Quirini as well as articles discussing key topics like the IUE/UE split, strikes and McCarthyism may be found in Series 2. Clippings about pension rights and retiree demonstrations may be found in Series 5.
  Issues of UE Local 301 News and IUE Local 301 News, the newspapers of Local 301, are available in microfilm, paper and electronic format in the records of IUE Local 301, APAP-023.
  - General Electric Works News, 1917 January-1922 March 02 (Microfilm 1)
  - General Electric Works News, 1922 January 06-1925 June 19 (Microfilm 2)
  - General Electric Works News, 1925 July 03-1928 March 16 (Microfilm 3)
  - General Electric Works News, 1928 April 06-1929 December 20 (Microfilm 4)
  - General Electric Works News, 1930 January 03-1939 December 29 (Microfilm 5)
  - General Electric Works News, 1940 January 05-1944 December 29 (Microfilm 6)
  - General Electric Works News, 1945 January 05-1950 December 29 (Microfilm 7)
  - General Electric Works News, 1951 January 05-1954 December 17 (Microfilm 8)
  - General Electric Works News, 1955 January 07-1960 December 22 (Microfilm 9)
  - UE News, Local 201, Lynn, Massachusetts, 1953 (Oversized 9, Folder 1)
  - Union News; Erie Erie, Pennsylvania, 1954 (Oversized 9, Folder 2)
  - UE Local 107 News, 1954 (Oversized 9, Folder 3)
  - General Electric News Schenectady, New York. Originals, 1953; 1958-1960; 1966-1971; 1973-1983; 1986-1987 (Oversized 9, Folder 4)
  - District Three Leader, 1968-1971; 1973-1976; 1978-1985 (Oversized 10, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO News, 1970; 1975; 1978-1982 (Oversized 11, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Area Labor News, 1968-1971; 1973; 1975 (Oversized 11, Folder 2)
  - UE News (National), 1971 September 15-1971 October 18 (Oversized 12, Folder 1)
  - UE News (National), 1972 June 26-1975 December 15 (Oversized 13, Folder 1)
  - UE News (National), 1976 January 05-1977 December 05 (Oversized 14, Folder 1)
  - UE News (National), 1978 January 09-1979 December 03 (Oversized 15, Folder 1)
  - UE News (National), 1980 January 07-1982 September 13 (Oversized 16, Folder 1)
- General Electric, 1918-2007; Undated; 5; 6.88 cubic ft.
  This series contains a wide variety of materials pertaining to General Electric, especially its operations in Schenectady where Helen Quirini worked from 1941 until 1980. There are files related to GE's corporate and administrative operations, such as annual reports and benefits information, materials illustrating Quirini's participation in the GE Athletic Association and her work with the Share Fund, and a scrapbook created by Quirini of the history of GE in Schenectady. Of interest to researchers may be files addressing work at GE during World War II, materials from the GE Apprentice Alumni Association and publications issued by GE.
  A significant number of files discuss GE retirees and their fights to secure better pensions, especially cost-of-living allowances. As a president and member of the Local 301 Retirees Council and a founding member of the GE Retirees Justice Fund, Quirini was active and extremely outspoken for the rights of retirees during the last 30 years of her life. This series documents her efforts in this fight, including picketing at GE offices and annual meetings, organizing rallies, introducing shareholder proposals and addressing GE executives at the annual meeting, corresponding with Jack Welch and Jeffrey Immelt during their respective tenures as chairman of the board and chief executive officer of GE and conducting media outreach. As a result, she was featured in many news articles and playwright Gail George created a one woman show in 1999 about Quirini's struggles for retiree rights with GE management, entitled Helen and Jack. There are several folders about the play Helen and Jack. Correspondence documenting Quirini's friendship with George as well as video of George's performances also are in the series.
  This series features correspondence, news clippings, photographs, subject files, pamphlets, pay stubs, reports, background materials, manuals, speeches, audio/video, news releases and media advisories.
  Please see Series 2 and 3 for more information about Quirini's labor union experiences while working at GE.
  - 2 Day Strike over Health, 2003 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 1)
  - 13th Pension Check, 2003 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 2)
  - 40th Anniversary Celebration, Schenectady Works Apprentice Alumni Association, 1941 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 3)
  - 60th Anniversary Celebration, Schenectady GE Apprentice Alumni Association, 1973 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 4)
  - 70th Anniversary Celebration, Schenectady GE Apprentice Alumni Association, 1983 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 5)
  - A.C. Stevens Letter re: Work Stoppage, 1956 September 20 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 6)
  - Adrian Braetens (Marion), Undated (Cassette 29)
  - AFL-CIO Retirees, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 7)
  - Anne P./Helen Rally, 2007 (Dvd 16)
  - Annual Meeting, Agenda, Report and Notes, 2000; 2008 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting, Shareholder Proposals, 1977; 1999-2008; 2010; Undated (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting, News Clips, 1997-1999; 2001-2009; Undated (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting, Notices and Proxy Statements, 2003; 2005 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting, Speeches, 1983-2003; Undated (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 12-13)
  - Annual Reports, 1975-1979 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 1990 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 19)
  - Annual Reports, 1991 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 20)
  - Annual Reports, 1992 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 21)
  - Annual Reports, 1993 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 22)
  - Annual Reports, 1994 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 23)
  - Annual Reports, 1995 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 24)
  - Annual Reports, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (5-General Electric), Folder 25)
  - Annual Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 2006 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 4)
  - Antonelli, Hank, 1994; 1998; 2004; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 5)
  - Application and Wage Data, 1967; 1970; 1977; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 6)
  - Badges for Employees, Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 7)
  - Benefits for Retirees, 1982-1999; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 8-9)
  - Benefits Pamphlets, 1966; 1970; 1973; 1976-1977 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 10)
  - Benefits Pamphlets, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 11)
  - Benefits Pamphlets, Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 12)
  - Benefits Update, 1997-2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 13)
  - Bessie Hunt and Edna Miller Interview on GE, by Gerald Zahavi and Elizabeth Griffin, 1992 August 24 (Cassette 30)
  - Buttons and Ribbons, Including Ones About Pension Rights, 1994; Undated (Oversized 7)
  - Carey, Jim, 1988; 1991; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 14)
  - CDC Retiree Leadership Meeting, 2007 March 15 (Dvd 17)
  - City and State Resolutions about Pensions, Layoffs and GE, 1954; 1986-2004; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 15)
  - City Council Resolution, GE, Undated (Video-tape 67)
  - City Council Meeting on GE, 2007 March 26 (Video-tape 68)
  - Class Action, 1955; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 16)
  - Class Action 401(K), 2006 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 17)
  - Class Action-Other Information, 1944-1995 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 18)
  - Coalition for Pension Security, 1997-1999; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 19)
  - Company Town (Helen Quirini), Undated (Video-tape 69)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, GE Apprentice Alumni Association, 1951; 1964; 1974 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 20)
  - Contract Proposal, 1960 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1989; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1990-2000 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 2001-1005; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 2008-2010; Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 26)
  - Current News, 1973-1975 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 27)
  - Declines in Percentage in Hourly Workers, 1978 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 28)
  - Directory of Graduates, 50th Anniversary Apprentice Training Courses Schenectady Works, 1951 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 29)
  - Discrimination Literature, 1954; 1972; 1974; 1978 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 30)
  - Divorce (Jack Welch), 2002-2003; 2005-2006 (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 31)
  - Dom Pitucci, 1999 July 19 (Cassette 31)
  - Donald Dietz, 1999 July 23 (Cassette 32)
  - Edna Miller, 1998 January 25 (Cassette 33)
  - Employees Community Service Fund, Undated (Box 2 (5-General Electric), Folder 32)
  - Employees Share Fund, 1972-1977; 1987; Undated (Box 3 (5-General Electric), Folder 1)
  - Erie Graduate Apprentice, 50th Anniversary, 1960 (Box 3 (5-General Electric), Folder 2)